<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on ngin</title>
    <link>https://tntech-ngin.net/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on ngin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 08:35:25 +0545</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tntech-ngin.net/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Master&#39;s Defense - David Reddick</title>
      <link>https://tntech-ngin.net/david/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 12:21:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tntech-ngin.net/david/</guid>
      <description>David Reddick has successfully defended his master&amp;rsquo;s thesis - &amp;ldquo;Design of an Ndn-Based Data Distribution Infrastructure for Genomics Data Secured With a Novel Ledger Access System Founded on Attribute-Based Encryption&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Science Foundation Research Experiences for Undergraduates (REU): Science DMZ Performance Measurement</title>
      <link>https://tntech-ngin.net/reu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 12:21:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tntech-ngin.net/reu/</guid>
      <description>This Research Experience for Undergraduates (REU) program is a National Science Foundation (NSF) funded research program at Tennessee Tech University. We have 2-3 positions over the Fall 2021 and Spring 2022 semesters. The undergraduate research assistants will learn to perform research under the guidance of Computer Science faculties. We welcome applications from all current undergraduate students at Tennessee Tech with strong interests in systems areas such as high-performance computing, networking, and distributed systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master&#39;s Defense -  Robert Thompson</title>
      <link>https://tntech-ngin.net/robert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 12:21:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tntech-ngin.net/robert/</guid>
      <description>Robert Thompson has successfully defended his masters thesis - &amp;ldquo;An Efficient Vehicle-to-Everything Charging Coordination Protocol for Electric Vehicles Using Named Data Networking&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiring Ph.D. Students</title>
      <link>https://tntech-ngin.net/phd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 12:21:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tntech-ngin.net/phd/</guid>
      <description>Multiple Fully Funded Ph.D. Positions at the Next Generation Networking Lab
Tennessee Technological University, Cookeville, TN, USA
 We are looking for motivated students to work on several next-generation networking topics. The students will study, design, build, and deploy next-generation network infrastructure and protocols for various use cases such as Augmented Reality/Virtual Reality(AR/VR), Domain Science applications with Big Data (e.g., Climate Science, Genomics, Physics), Content Delivery Networks (CDNs), 5G mobile networks, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NSF REU Grant Award</title>
      <link>https://tntech-ngin.net/news/science-dmz-reu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 20:15:07 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tntech-ngin.net/news/science-dmz-reu/</guid>
      <description>Prof. Shannigrahi and Prof. Rogers have been awarded a National Science Foundation REU Grant to investigate the effects of an ScienceDMZ on a campus infrastructure. Link
ScienceDMZ networks are widely deployed in US academic campuses. However, there is a lack of studies around how ScienceDMZs influence actual scientific data and workflows. This supplemental project will design and perform a measurement study that will quantify the improvements brought forward by the new science DMZ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High Performance Error Free File Transfer</title>
      <link>https://tntech-ngin.net/news/tntech-hipft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 20:15:07 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tntech-ngin.net/news/tntech-hipft/</guid>
      <description>Prof. Shannigrahi in collaboration with Colorado State University has been awarded a National Science Foundation Grant to investigate errors that happen in the Internet. This measurement and error detection/correction study will not only improve our understanding of Internet errors but also improve large data transfers over the Internet. Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee Tech Science DMZ</title>
      <link>https://tntech-ngin.net/news/tntech-science-dmz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 20:15:07 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tntech-ngin.net/news/tntech-science-dmz/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Prof. Shannigrahi and Prof. Rogers has received a $263K grant from National Science Foundation to create a Science DMZ at Tennessee Tech.
Created in collaboration with IT services, this project will enhance movement of large datasets to and from the campus. It will also
bring IPV6 deployment to the campus. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nsf.gov/awardsearch/showAward?AWD_ID=2018373&#34;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
